# ADAM T'KOY

https://www.linkedin.com/in/adam-tkoy/ https://github.com/AdamTKoy a.p.tkoy@gmail.com | 630-363-0924

With a strong foundation in computer science from a top-ranked university, I quickly adjust to new technologies and problem solving challenges. I push myself to deliver my highest quality work and achieve goals while always turning work into fun. Most of all, I love to collaborate because working with amazing people has been the highlight of all my prior experiences.

#### **SKILLS**

- Proficient in C, C++, Java, Python, and R using IDEs like R-Studio, Visual Studio, and Xcode
- Led as front-end developer for semester-long group project creating web app with React, Node.js
- Completed additional learning outside degree in JavaScript, MongoDB, Python Pandas, SQL, Swift
- Experience coding in a Linux environment, including implementing a simplified version of shell
- · Experience debugging code with GDB and checking memory use with Valgrind
- · Experience with version control using GitHub for both solo and group projects

#### **EDUCATION**

## University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign

August 2024

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Computer Science

GPA: 3.91/4.00

Coursework included: Computer Architecture, Linear Algebra, Programming Languages & Compilers, Software Design Lab, Statistics Programming Methods, System Programming

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Genius Admin Naperville, IL

Apple Store

March 2022 - August 2023

- Efficiently resolved repair issues
- Tracked progress of repairs both in-store and at offsite repair facility
- Collaborated across store teams to ensure excellent customer experiences
- Received a merit bonus 3 times for performance and dedication

#### Career Experience

Cupertino, CA

Apple

January 2023 - June 2023

Supported the Manufacturing Quality Engineering, Color team for 5 months, full-time:

- Operated special equipment to measure samples for color and texture
- Cleaned and manipulated data in Tableau to generate summary reports and visualizations
- Coordinated parts during sample reviews with Industrial Design team
- Sorted, packaged, and labeled limit samples for long-term archival project

### **Product Specialist**

Naperville, IL

Apple Store

November 2019 - March 2022

• Consistently generated revenue for the store while efficiently creating solutions for a high volume of customers, including sales support, data migration/initial setup, and basic troubleshooting

## **Program Support Specialist**

Glen Ellyn, IL

College of DuPage

December 2017 - November 2019

Supported the improvement manager for Career and Technical Education (CTE) Programs with administrative tasks, including:

- Analyzed student data to create and update statistical reports each semester
- Updated 3 internal data resource websites using HTML